<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tags on Tulsa Bike Polo Club</title>
    <link>https://tulsabikepolo.netlify.app/tags/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tags on Tulsa Bike Polo Club</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://tulsabikepolo.netlify.app/tags/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>https://tulsabikepolo.netlify.app/posts/coc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Dec 2023 22:49:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tulsabikepolo.netlify.app/posts/coc/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Tulsa Bike Polo Club (TBPC) welcomes everyone and aspires to create diverse,
inclusive, and supportive spaces. Whether at the court, on our social media, at club sponsored
events, or elsewhere – the following apply:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No member shall engage in any conduct, act towards, or speak to or of any other person
in a manner which offends, insults, humiliates or vilifies such person on the basis of
gender identity, sexual preference, race, religion, descent, ethnic origin, or ability.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Members are expected to conduct themselves in a manner that will enhance the
reputation of TBPC and bike polo in general, both on and off the court.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Members will avoid engaging in any form of conduct or behavior detrimental to the spirit
of the game as well as treat other players, spectators, and property respectfully.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No intimidation or abusive language or behavior will be tolerated on or off the court.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;safer-spaces-guidelines&#34;&gt;Safer Spaces Guidelines&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Respect people’s background and identities, including their names and pronouns.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be thoughtful about the language you use.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you believe someone has violated our COC, feel free to speak up and/or inform a club
member.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Allow others to call you in if they believe you may have acted in violation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Allow others to represent and speak for themselves – never ask or expect someone to
speak on behalf of others.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Let others learn at their own pace and ask before giving advice.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;accountability-process&#34;&gt;Accountability Process&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;TBPC encourages individuals to resolve conflict amongst themselves by privately giving
constructive, respectful feedback if it feels safe to do so. All members shall focus on receiving
feedback in a manner that seeks to understand, collaborate, and implement a solution.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another club member may occasionally be asked to act as a conflict mediator between two or
more parties. A mediator’s role is to be objective/impartial, focused on enhancing respectful
language, and suggesting possible solutions. The conflict mediator should not be the go-to
person at every instance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All members shall hold themselves accountable for adhering to and promoting the CoC in a
manner that is proactive and intentional. If members find themselves unable to do so, they may
be subject to ejection from a game or suspension at the discretion of the club majority.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sources&lt;/strong&gt;: Austin, East Van, Lafayette, &amp;amp; Portland Bike Polo CoC&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
